mcdelivery.co.in 2017-04-17

# Home

Thank you for visiting us online at [www.mcdonaldsindia.com](http://www.mcdonaldsindia.com/) (“website” or “our website”). 

Hardcastle Restaurants Private Limited (HRPL) is a wholly owned subsidiary of Westlife Development Limited listed on BSE (Bombay Stock Exchange) with scrip code 505533, which focuses on putting up and operating Quick Service Restaurants (QSRs) in West and South India. HRPL is a franchisee of McDonald’s India Private Limited (MIPL) with rights to own and operate restaurants under the brand name “McDonald’s” in India’s West and South markets. 

At HRPL, we strive to do everything we can to respect the trust customers have in our brand, and our commitment to your privacy is no exception. We are committed to protecting and safeguarding consumer’s privacy on the internet, especially for children. 

**HRPL’S INTERNET PRIVACY POLICY**

HRPL is pleased to provide information to all of its customers about its online privacy policy. Please be assured that HRPL uses its best efforts to protect the privacy of visitors to this website. 

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes the types of personal information we collect from visitors to our website and users of our Mobile Applications (collectively “Online Services”). This Policy not only sets forth how we use this information, but also provides other details about our personal information practices, and explains how to contact us if you have any questions or concerns. 

**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW IT IS USED**

When using Online Services i.e. when ordering or registering on HRPL’s website or Mobile Applications, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number or other details. HRPL gathers such personal information only when voluntarily submitted by you. e.g., personal information may be collected from you in order to get your feedback on our website and our products, or to improve our website in order to serve you better, or to quickly process your transactions, or to ensure your entry in one of our contests or sweepstakes. If you do not agree or consent to submission of such information, you will not be allowed to register yourself or participate in our contests, sweepstakes or use any functions on our website which require such personal information to be submitted. 

**SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

HRPL may share personal information within the McDonald’s Family. The McDonald’s Family includes McDonald’s Corporation, our franchisees, our subsidiaries and our affiliates. Of course, any use of this information by the McDonald’s Family will comply with this Policy. Occasionally, we will send marketing information to you, such as discount coupons, information about new product offerings, etc. If you elect not to receive such materials, we will not send them to you. 

In addition, when you visit our website or use Online Services, we may collect certain information by automated means. The information we collect may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, computer/mobile device operating system and browser type, type of mobile device, the location of mobile device, the Unique Device Identifier (UDID) or Mobile Equipment Identifier (MEID), the network carrier or any other information about your mobile device, the address of a referring website (if any), and the pages you visit on our website. We may use this information to operate, maintain, and manage our Online Services and to provide services such as technical support. We provide additional information regarding our use of “cookies” in this Privacy Policy below. 

**MOBILE DEVICES AND LOCATION INFORMATION**

Mobile Apps may collect precise information about the location of your mobile device using technologies such as GPS, Wi-Fi, or cell tower proximity. HRPL uses this information for location-based services that you request such as locating nearby McDonald’s restaurants or identifying special offers that may be of interest to you. For most mobile devices, you are able to withdraw your permission for HRPL to acquire this information on your location through the device settings. If you have questions about how to disable your mobile device’s location services, we recommend you contact your mobile device service provider or the device manufacturer. If you would like us to delete location information we have collected, please contact us at the email or postal address listed below. Please note that the applications may not function properly following deletion, and that we may be required by law to retain certain information. 

HRPL does not sell personal information to third parties outside the McDonald’s Family though, with your permission, such personal information may be, subject to compliance with this Policy, transferred, shared or disclosed to third parties including third party service providers outside the McDonald’s Family. Such personal information shall however be transferred, shared or disclosed securely via modern cryptography e.g. over HTTPS. In case personal information (which includes the online behavioural analysis of the user of Online Services) is shared, transferred or disclosed to third party service providers, it shall be done so only for the purpose of personalizing your online ordering experience With your permission, we will, on occasion send marketing information on behalf of one of our business partners about products or services they provide that may be of interest to you. You may be asked if you wish to receive marketing materials from McDonald’s business partners. If you elect to receive such materials, HRPL will not share your personal information with such partners but rather will send a mailer or email on behalf of the partners. 

HRPL reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the sites, to fulfil your requests, or to co-operate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a matter of public safety. 

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY NOTICE**

HRPL understands the importance of privacy to visitors to and users of our Online Services. We are especially committed to protecting the privacy of children who visit or use our Online Services. 

**A .** |  **   WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  
---|---  
**1 .** |   We offer many features on our website, like games and other activities, which do not require a child to provide any personal information. On occasion, however, we may collect personal information, such as an email address from children as part of an activity. For example: We may collect a child’s email address to notify the child if he or she has won or lost a contest or activity. In that event, we will notify the child using the email address the child supplies. We will not keep the address or use it for any other purpose.   
---|---  
**2 .** |   We may collect a child’s email address in order to respond to a request from the child on a one-time basis, such as to send the child a screen saver. In this case we promptly delete the email address from our system once we have responded, and we do not use the address for any other purpose.   
**3 .** |   HRPL will not condition a child’s participation in any online activity on the child’s disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in that activity.   
**B .** |  **HOW DO WE USE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT?**  
---|---  
**1 .** |   We use email addresses submitted by a child in order to respond to the child’s request or to notify the child if he or she has won or lost a contest or activity they entered.   
---|---  
**C .** |  **HOW DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
---|---  
We may share a child’s personal information with third parties to the extent reasonably necessary to protect the security or integrity of our Online Services, take precautions against liability, or respond to judicial process or requests from other governmental authorities; or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.   
---  
**1 .** | We also may share personal information collected by us with vendors that perform services for HRPL. These services may include hosting our website, providing technical services to HRPL, fulfilling requests or administering activities.   
  
**ACCESS**

You are in control of any personal information you provide us on-line. If at any time, you would like to correct the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contacts from us or on behalf of our business partners, you can let us know by contacting us at the email or postal address listed below. 

**COOKIES**

“Cookies” are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies allow the website to remember important information that will make your use of the sites more convenient. Like most websites, HRPL uses cookies for a variety of purposes in order to improve your on-line experience. e.g., we track the total number of visitors to our website on an anonymous aggregate basis. We may also employ cookies so that we remember you when you return to the sites, to keep track of the items/pages you view on our website to help us customize your experience. 

We may associate personal information with a cookie file in those instances. 

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

The policies of HRPL’s website may vary from other McDonald’s sites operated by other McDonald’s entities, however because of local customs, practices or laws or due to circumstances unique to those sites. In all cases, however, we will honour the commitments to our customers set forth in this policy regarding the collection and use of personal information. 

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

If we change our Policy, we will post the revised version here, so we suggest that you check here periodically for the most up-to-date version of our Policy. Your continued use of the sites will be deemed acceptance of the Policy. Rest assured, however, that any changes will not be retroactively applied and will not alter how we handle previously collected information. 

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about HRPL’s Internet Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

Hardcastle Restaurants Private Limited 

1001 - 1002, Tower - 3, 10th floor,  
Indiabulls Finance Centre,  
Senapati Bapat Marg,  
Elphinstone Road, Mumbai - 400013  
T: 022 - 49135000; F: 022 – 49135001  
Email: [myfeedback@mcdonaldsindia.com](http://www.mcdonaldsindia.com/myfeedback@mcdonaldsindia.com)
